A Guide to the Virginia War History Commission, 1915-1931
Library of Virginia
- City Source Material, 1919-1927
  - Petersburg
    - Virginia Schools and Colleges
      - Petersburg Schools (Box 68, Folder 2)
      - Southern College (Box 68, Folder 3)
      - Virginia Normal and Industrial Institute (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Draft Law and Virginia Organizations
      - Partial List of Petersburg Soldiers, n.d. (Box 68, Folder 5)
      - Frank Baylor Blanchard - Service Record (Box 68, Folder 6)
      - A.P. Hill Rifles, Muster Roll, 1917-1919 (Box 68, Folder 7)
      - Casualty List (Box 68, Folder 8)
      - Central State Hosptial Men Who Served in the World War (Box 68, Folder 9)
      - Draft Day (Box 68, Folder 10)
      - Draft Registrants of 1917-1918 (Box 68, Folder 11)
      - Petersburg Dentists in the Army (Box 68, Folder 12)
      - Draft Registrants, 1918 and clippings (Box 68, Folder 13)
      - Miscellaneous Clippings, Rosters, 1919 (Box 68, Folder 14)
      - Petersburg Doctors in the Service (Box 68, Folder 15)
      - Petersburg Greys (Box 68, Folder 16)
      - Petersburg Guard (Box 68, Folder 17)
      - V.M.I. Men from Petersburg in the War (Box 68, Folder 18)
      - War Record of Tarlton F. Persons (Box 68, Folder 19)
    - Virginia Camps and Cantonments - "The Bayonet - Remembrance Book of Camp Lee" and Miscellaneous Photographs of Camp Lee (Box 68, Folder 20)
    - Economic and Social Conditions
      - Chamber of Commerce [See Also Oversize Box 4, Folder 3] (Box 68, Folder 21)
      - Civilian Committee for Prevention of Vice (Box 68, Folder 22)
      - Civilian Committee on Law Enforcement (Box 68, Folder 23)
      - Committee of Protection of Girls and Young Women (Box 68, Folder 24)
      - Farm Land Bank (Box 68, Folder 25)
      - Food Conservation (Box 68, Folder 26)
      - Fuel Administration (Box 68, Folder 27)
      - Health Sanitation; Influenza Epidemic (Box 68, Folder 28)
      - History of Liberty Theater (Box 68, Folder 29)
      - Juvenile Protective Association (Box 68, Folder 30)
      - Labor (Box 68, Folder 31)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 68, Folder 32)
      - Municipal Health Department (Box 68, Folder 33)
      - Naturalization of Aliens at Camp Lee (Box 68, Folder 34)
      - Sings at Camp Lee and Record of Father Driscoll (Box 68, Folder 35)
      - Venereal Clinic (Box 68, Folder 36)
      - War Saving Stamps (Box 68, Folder 37)
    - War Work and Relief Organizations (Box 68, Folder 38)
    - War Letters and Incidents
      - Adams, Edward D'Arcey (Vol. III, p. 1) (Box 69, Folder 1)
      - Anonymous (Vol. III, p. 3) (Box 69, Folder 2)
      - Anonymous (omitted from Volume III) (Box 69, Folder 3)
      - Aspeslugh, Henri (Vol. III, p. 4) (Box 69, Folder 4)
      - Barksdale, Edward Marcellus (Vol. III, p. 5) (Box 69, Folder 5)
      - Bolling, Robert C. (Vol. III, p. 7) (Box 69, Folder 6)
      - Bourgeois, Jene (omitted from Volume III) (Box 69, Folder 7)
      - Bragg, Archie A. (Vol. III, p. 8) (Box 69, Folder 8)
      - Capoen, Couiele (Vol. III, p. 10) (Box 69, Folder 9)
      - Carr, Robert (Vol. III, p. 11) (Box 69, Folder 10)
      - Clements, Austin (Vol. III, p. 12) (Box 69, Folder 11)
      - Cronkhite, Adelbert (Vol. III, p. 16) (Box 69, Folder 12)
      - Dandridge, Edmund Pendleton (Vol. III, p. 16) (Box 69, Folder 13)
      - Dempsey, Earl H. (omitted from Volume III) (Box 69, Folder 14)
      - Drewry, W.F. (Vol. III, p. 18) (Box 69, Folder 15)
      - Duke, James P. (Vol. III, p. 18) (Box 69, Folder 16)
      - Ellis, J. Tyler (Vol. III, p. 19) (Box 69, Folder 17)
      - Fitz, George (Vol. III, p. 20) (Box 69, Folder 18)
      - George, Howard H. (Vol. III, p. 22) (Box 69, Folder 19)
      - Gilliam, William C. (Vol. III, p. 22) (Box 69, Folder 20)
      - Higgins, George (omitted from Volume III) (Box 69, Folder 21)
      - Ivey, George T. (Vol. III, p. 29) (Box 69, Folder 22)
      - Lewis, Charles Wheeler (Vol. III, p. 34) (Box 69, Folder 23)
      - Lyon, Leroy Springs (biography) (Box 69, Folder 24)
      - Matthews, Paul (Vol. III, p. 37) (Box 69, Folder 25)
      - Reinhord, John J. (Vol. III, p. 46) (Box 69, Folder 26)
      - Ridenour, Cyrus E. (Vol. III, p. 46) (Box 69, Folder 27)
      - Ridout, Wallace (Vol. III, p. 46) (Box 69, Folder 28)
      - Rittenhouse, George F. (Vol. III, p. 47) (Box 69, Folder 29)
      - Sanders, Edgar (Vol. III, p. 51) (Box 69, Folder 30)
      - Saveyn, Omar (Vol. III, p. 51) (Box 69, Folder 31)
      - Smith, Jr., Hier L. (omitted from Volume III) (Box 69, Folder 32)
      - Smith, Jr., Horace L. (Vol. III, p. 53) (Box 69, Folder 33)
      - Strailman, Frank O. (Vol. III, p. 55) (Box 69, Folder 34)
      - Wilson, T.P. (Vol. III, p. 63) (Box 69, Folder 35)
      - Slang Phrases and Their Meaning as Used by Men at Camp Lee (Box 69, Folder 36)
      - Issues of "The Daily Smoke" (Box 69, Folder 37)
      - Miscellaneous Clippings (Box 69, Folder 38)
      - Proclamation of the President of the United States, 1 June 1918 (Box 69, Folder 39)
      - War Poems (Box 69, Folder 40)
      - War Poems by Arthur Kyle Davis, Jr. (Box 69, Folder 41)
      - War Songs (Box 69, Folder 42)
    - Post-War Conditions and Activities (Box 69, Folder 43)
    - Miscellaneous Clippings (Box 69, Folder 44)
    - Miscellaneous - Official Statement of Rhodes Committee of Virginia, ca. 1919, selecting Arthur Kyle Davis, Jr. (Box 69, Folder 45)
  - Portsmouth
    - Virginians of Distinguished Service (lists) (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Pre-War Conditions and Activities (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Churches in War Time
      - Monumental M.E. Church (Box 70, Folder 3)
      - Park View Methodist Church (Box 70, Folder 4)
      - Presbyterian Church (Box 70, Folder 5)
      - St. Paul's Catholic Church (Box 70, Folder 6)
      - Trinity Church (Box 70, Folder 7)
      - Unidentified Church (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Economic and Social Conditions (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - War Work and Relief Organizations (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - War Work and Relief Organizations (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - War Letters and Incidents
      - Neville, Wendell C. (Clipping from Portsmouth Star, 14 March 1920) [See Oversize Box 4, Folder 4] (Box 70, Folder 12)
      - Incomplete List of War Dead (Box 70, Folder 13)
    - Post-War Conditions and Activities (Box 70, Folder 14)
  - Radford
    - Virginia Communities in War Time - Radford City in War Time by Sadie Johnson Reid (Box 70, Folder 15)
    - Virginia Communities in War Time - Radford in the War by G.E. Cassel (Box 70, Folder 16)
    - Virginia Churches in War Time (Box 70, Folder 17)
    - War Work and Relief Organizations (Box 70, Folder 18)
    - War Letters and Incidents - Miscellaneous (Box 70, Folder 19)
  - Richmond
    - Richmond City in War Time
      - Chapter 1 - Pre-War Conditions and Activities - Drafts and Notes (Box 71, Folder 1)
      - Chapter 3 - Schools and Colleges - Drafts and Notes (Box 71, Folder 2)
      - Chapter 4 - Draft and Military Organizations - Drafts and Notes (Box 71, Folder 3)
      - Chapter 5 - Economic and Social Conditions - Drafts and Notes (Box 71, Folder 4)
      - Chapter 5 - Economic and Social Conditions - Drafts and Notes (Box 71, Folder 5)
      - Chapter 6 - Red Cross - Drafts and Notes (Box 71, Folder 6)
      - Chapter 7 - War Work and Relief Organizations - Drafts and Notes (Box 71, Folder 7)
      - Chapter 8 - Post-War Conditions and Activities - Drafts and Notes (Box 71, Folder 8)
      - Partial List of Richmond City Source Material (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Virginians of Distinguished Service
      - Civilian - List and Sketches of Nominees (Box 72, Folder 2)
      - Civilian - Anderson, Henry W. (Box 72, Folder 3)
      - Civilian - Branch, John Kerr (Box 72, Folder 4)
      - Civilian - Byrd, Harry Flood (Box 72, Folder 5)
      - Civilian - Calish, Rabbi E.N. (Box 72, Folder 6)
      - Civilian - Freeman, Douglas Southall (Box 72, Folder 7)
      - Civilian - Keiley, C.R. (Box 72, Folder 8)
      - Civilian - MacLachlan, H.D.C. (Box 72, Folder 9)
      - Civilian - Millhiser, Mrs. Loulie (Box 72, Folder 10)
      - Civilian - Seay, George J. (Box 72, Folder 11)
      - Civilian - Stern, Jo Lane (Box 72, Folder 12)
      - Civilian - Strauss, Lewis L. (Box 72, Folder 13)
      - Civilian - Williams, John Skelton (Box 72, Folder 14)
      - Civilian - Miscellaneous Women (Box 72, Folder 15)
      - Military - List (Box 72, Folder 16)
    - Pre-War Conditions and Activities
      - Pre-War Developments in Richmond (Box 72, Folder 17)
    - Virginia Churches in War Time
      - Richmond Churches (Box 72, Folder 18)
      - Richmond Churches (duplicate) (Box 72, Folder 19)
      - All Saints Episcopal Church (Box 72, Folder 20)
      - Bainbridge Street Baptist Church (Box 72, Folder 21)
      - Barton Heights Methodist Church (Box 72, Folder 22)
      - Beth Ahabah (Box 72, Folder 23)
      - Bethlehem Evangelical Lutheran Church (Box 72, Folder 24)
      - Branch Memorial M.E. Church (Box 72, Folder 25)
      - Broad Street Methodist Episcopal Church (Box 72, Folder 26)
      - Broadus Memorial Baptist Church (Box 72, Folder 27)
      - Calvary Baptist (Box 72, Folder 28)
      - Catholic Churches (Box 73, Folder 1)
      - Centenary Methodist Church (Box 73, Folder 2)
      - Central M.E. Church (Box 73, Folder 3)
      - Christ Church (Box 73, Folder 4)
      - Clopton Street Baptist (Box 73, Folder 5)
      - Daughters of the King, St. Mark's Church (Box 73, Folder 6)
      - Decatur Street Methodist Episcopal Church (Box 73, Folder 7)
      - Denny Street Methodist Church (Box 73, Folder 8)
      - Epiphany Episcopal Church (Box 73, Folder 9)
      - First Baptist Church (Box 73, Folder 10)
      - First Presbyterian Church (Box 73, Folder 11)
      - Ginter Park Baptist Church (Box 73, Folder 12)
      - Grace Covenant Presbyterian Church (Box 73, Folder 13)
      - Grace Episcopal Church (Box 73, Folder 14)
      - Grace Methodist Church (Clay Street Methodist Church) (Box 73, Folder 15)
      - Grace Street Baptist Church (Box 73, Folder 16)
      - Grove Avenue Baptist Church (Box 73, Folder 17)
      - Hanover Avenue Christian Church (Box 73, Folder 18)
      - Holy Comforter Episcopal Church (Box 73, Folder 19)
      - Holy Trinity Church (Box 73, Folder 20)
      - Laurel Street Methodist Church (Box 73, Folder 21)
      - Meade Memorial Church (Box 73, Folder 22)
      - Mizpah Presbyterian Church (Box 73, Folder 23)
      - Monument Methodist Church (Box 73, Folder 24)
      - Monumental Episcopal Church (Box 73, Folder 25)
      - Overbrook Presbyterian Church (Box 73, Folder 26)
      - Pace Memorial Methodist Episcopal Church, South (Box 73, Folder 27)
      - Park Place Methodist Episcopal Church (Box 73, Folder 28)
      - Porter Street Presbyterian Church (Box 73, Folder 29)
      - Randolph Street Baptist Church (Box 73, Folder 30)
      - St. Andrew's Episcopal Church (Box 73, Folder 31)
      - St. James M.E. Church (Box 73, Folder 32)
      - St. James Church (Box 73, Folder 33)
      - St. John's Evangelical Church (Box 73, Folder 34)
      - St. John's P.E. Church (Box 73, Folder 35)
      - St. Marks' Episcopal Church (Box 73, Folder 36)
      - St. Paul's (Box 73, Folder 37)
      - St. Thomas Church, Ginter Park (Box 73, Folder 38)
      - Second Baptist Church (Box 73, Folder 39)
      - Second Presbyterian Church (Box 73, Folder 40)
      - Seventh Street Christian Church (Box 73, Folder 41)
      - Sixth Mount Zion Baptist Church (Box 73, Folder 42)
      - Stockton Street Church (Box 73, Folder 43)
      - Third Presbyterian Church (Box 73, Folder 44)
      - Trinity Methodist Episcopal Church (Box 74, Folder 1)
      - Union Station M.E. Church (Box 74, Folder 2)
      - Unitarian Church (Box 74, Folder 3)
      - Weatherford Memorial Baptist (Box 74, Folder 4)
      - West End Memorial M.E. Church (Box 74, Folder 5)
      - Westhampton Baptist Church (Box 74, Folder 6)
      - Woodland Hights M.E. (Box 74, Folder 7)
      - Miscellaneous issues of The League Record (Presbyterian League of Richmond) (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - Virginia Schools and Colleges
      - Bethlehem Lutheran School (Box 74, Folder 9)
      - Catholic Parochial Schools (Box 74, Folder 10)
      - Collegiate School (Box 74, Folder 11)
      - Hartshorn Memorial College (Box 74, Folder 12)
      - John Marshall High School (Box 74, Folder 13)
      - Massey Business College (Box 74, Folder 14)
      - McGuire's University School (Box 74, Folder 15)
      - Medical College of Virginia (Box 74, Folder 16)
      - Mount Marie Convent (Box 74, Folder 17)
      - Public Schools - War Activities, 1917-1918 (Box 74, Folder 18)
      - Public Schools - War Activities, 1918-1919 (Box 74, Folder 19)
      - Richmond College (Box 74, Folder 20)
      - Richmond and Westhampton College (Box 74, Folder 21)
      - Richmond and Westhampton College - Copies of Heads Up - Newspaper of Debarkation Hospital 52 (Box 74, Folder 22)
      - Richmond and Westhampton College - Copies of Heads Up - Newspaper of Debarkation Hospital 52 (Box 74, Folder 23)
      - St. Christopher's School (Box 74, Folder 24)
      - School of Social Work (Box 74, Folder 25)
      - Smithdeal Business College (Box 74, Folder 26)
      - University of Richmond (Box 74, Folder 27)
      - Van de Vyver (Box 74, Folder 28)
      - Virginia Mechanics Institute (Box 74, Folder 29)
      - Virginia Randolph Ellett School (Box 74, Folder 30)
      - Virginia Union University (Box 74, Folder 31)
    - Draft Law and Military Organizations
      - Richmond Men Who Died of Disease During World War (Box 74, Folder 32)
      - Home Defense League of Richmond (Box 74, Folder 33)
      - Roster of Home Defense League (Box 74, Folder 34)
      - Roster of Home Defense League, 1st Unit, 3rd District (Box 74, Folder 35)
      - Roster of Home Defense League, 2nd Company, 3rd Police District, 1 January 1918 (Box 74, Folder 36)
      - List of Nearest Relatives of those who Died in Service (Box 74, Folder 37)
      - List of Soldiers Richmond Commission Needs More Information (Box 74, Folder 38)
      - List of Negro Soldiers with Addresses (Box 74, Folder 39)
      - Richmond Men Killed During the War (Box 74, Folder 40)
      - Sketch of Randolph Fitzhugh Mason (Box 74, Folder 41)
      - Military Record of Dr. Charles R. Robins (Box 74, Folder 42)
      - Activities of Draft Board (Box 74, Folder 43)
      - List of Teachers who assisted Draft Board (Box 74, Folder 44)
      - Brief History of Selective Service Work in Virginia During the World War (Box 74, Folder 45)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 74, Folder 46)
      - Copy of World War Section of the History of Jews of Richmond (Box 74, Folder 47)
    - Economic and Social Conditions
      - Commerce - Commerce During the War (Box 74, Folder 48)
      - Commerce - Richmond Chamber of Commerce in War Work (Box 74, Folder 49)
      - Commerce - Tobacco Trade of Richmond's Part in the World War (Box 75, Folder 1)
      - Communication - Postal Service During the War (Box 75, Folder 2)
      - Communication - Telephones in the War (Box 75, Folder 3)
      - Communication - Western Union During the War (Box 75, Folder 4)
      - Finance - Boy Scouts in the War (Box 75, Folder 5)
      - Finance - War Savings Campaign of 1918 (Box 75, Folder 6)
      - Food - State Department of Agriculuture (Box 75, Folder 7)
      - Food - Distribution of Home Card (Box 75, Folder 8)
      - Food - Findings of Grand Jury on Profiteering (Box 75, Folder 9)
      - Food - Report of Food Administration Chairman (Box 75, Folder 10)
      - Food - Local Food Administration (Box 75, Folder 11)
      - Food - Minutes of the Central and General Committees of Woman's Co-operative Organizations of the Local Food Administration, 1918 (Box 75, Folder 12)
      - Food - Food Conservation and the Churches (Box 75, Folder 13)
      - Food - James River Garden Club (Box 75, Folder 14)
      - Food - War Time Activities, Agriculturally (Box 75, Folder 15)
      - Food - Women's Division, Council of Defense, Chairman of Food Production (Box 75, Folder 16)
      - Fuel - Federal Fuel Administration, History (Box 75, Folder 17)
      - Fuel - Federal Fuel Administration, Collection of Office Forms (Box 75, Folder 18)
      - Industry - American Locomotive Company (Box 75, Folder 19)
      - Industry - Richmond Forgings Corporation (Box 75, Folder 20)
      - Industry - Tredegar Iron Works (Box 75, Folder 21)
      - Industry - War Industries in Richmond (Box 75, Folder 22)
      - Labor - Effect of the War on the Attitude and Organization of Labor Groups (Box 75, Folder 23)
      - Labor - Labor Conditions in Richmond During the World War (Box 75, Folder 24)
      - Labor - Public Employment Bureau (Box 75, Folder 25)
      - Social - Social Life of Richmond During the World War (Box 75, Folder 26)
      - Social - Effect of War Status and Outlook of Women (Box 75, Folder 27)
      - Social - Four Minute Men (Box 75, Folder 28)
      - Social - Richmond's Literary Contribution to the War (Box 75, Folder 29)
      - Transportation and Communication (Box 75, Folder 30)
      - Transportation - Atlantic Coast Line Railroad (Box 75, Folder 31)
      - Transportation - United States Railroad Administration (Box 75, Folder 32)
      - Boy Scouts, Troop 9 (Box 75, Folder 33)
    - Red Cross in Virginia
      - "As You Like It" Auxiliary Report (Box 75, Folder 34)
      - Canteen Committee (Box 75, Folder 35)
      - Church of Good Shepherd - Red Cross Chapter (Box 75, Folder 36)
      - Home Services Section (Box 75, Folder 37)
      - History of the Hospital Supplies Committee (Box 75, Folder 38)
      - Knitting Department (Box 75, Folder 39)
      - Miller and Rhoads Red Cross Unit (Box 75, Folder 40)
      - Nursing Survey Committee (Box 75, Folder 41)
      - Red Cross Motor Corps (Box 75, Folder 42)
      - History of Richmond Virginia Chapter (Box 75, Folder 43)
      - Work of Richmond Chapter (Box 75, Folder 44)
      - Richmond Chapter, Colored Branch (Box 75, Folder 45)
      - Historical Sketch of Ambulance Company 319 (Red Cross Ambulance Company 46) (Box 75, Folder 46)
      - St. James Episcopal Church Red Cross Auxiliary (Box 75, Folder 47)
      - Smileage Book Campaign (Box 75, Folder 48)
      - Women who Received Medals for Red Cross Work (Box 75, Folder 49)
    - War Work and Relief Organizations
      - Partial List of Records (Box 76, Folder 1)
      - American Library Association Work (Box 76, Folder 2)
      - Army Navy Club - Library Report (Box 76, Folder 3)
      - Beth Ahabah Auxiliary (Box 76, Folder 4)
      - Beth Ahabah Canteen Service (Box 76, Folder 5)
      - Special War Work of Kate Langley Bosher (Box 76, Folder 6)
      - Camp Lee Festival for Sick and Wounded (Box 76, Folder 7)
      - Activities of the Catholic Women of Richmond (Box 76, Folder 8)
      - Camp Lee (Box 76, Folder 9)
      - Colonial Dames of America (Box 76, Folder 10)
      - Council of Jewish Women (Box 76, Folder 11)
      - Daughters of 1812 (Box 76, Folder 12)
      - Equal Suffrage League of Richmond (Box 76, Folder 13)
      - Fatherless Children of France (Box 76, Folder 14)
      - Godmother's League of Richmond (See Also Box 78) (Box 76, Folder 15)
      - Highland Park Woman's Club (Box 76, Folder 16)
      - James River Garden Club (Box 76, Folder 17)
      - Khaki and Blue Kitchen (Box 76, Folder 18)
      - Richmond Knights of Columbus (Box 76, Folder 19)
      - McGill Catholic Union (Box 76, Folder 20)
      - Musicians Club of Richmond (Box 76, Folder 21)
      - National Civic Federation (Box 76, Folder 22)
      - National League for Women's Services (Box 76, Folder 23)
      - Social Workers of Nurses' Settlement (Box 76, Folder 24)
      - Soldiers, Sailors and Marines Club (Box 76, Folder 25)
      - United Daughters of the Confederacy, Richmond Chapter (Box 76, Folder 26)
      - Virginia Anti-Tuberculosis Association (Box 76, Folder 27)
      - Virginia Association Opposed to Woman's Suffrage (Box 76, Folder 28)
      - War Camp Community Service in Richmond (Box 76, Folder 29)
      - War Camp Community Service in Virginia, 1917-1920, by R.C. Stearnes (Box 76, Folder 30)
      - History of the War Camp Community Service in Virginia from May 1917 through Demobilization (Box 76, Folder 31)
      - Review of National War Camp Community Service Work (Box 76, Folder 32)
      - War Camp Community Service - Miscellaneous (Box 76, Folder 33)
      - War Kitchen (Box 77, Folder 1)
      - War Relief Association (Box 77, Folder 2)
      - Woman's Club of Ginter Park (Box 77, Folder 3)
      - Woman's Club of Barton Heights (Box 77, Folder 4)
      - Woman's Land Army of America, Virginia Division (Box 77, Folder 5)
      - Woman's Auxiliary Camp Community Service - Minutes (Box 77, Folder 6)
      - Woman's Auxiliary Camp Community Service (Box 77, Folder 7)
      - Woman's Auxiliary War Camp, Narrative (Box 77, Folder 8)
      - Woman's Auxiliary of the Gray's Association (Box 77, Folder 9)
      - Woman's Auxiliary to the Howitzers Association (Box 77, Folder 10)
      - Women's Munitions Reserve (Box 77, Folder 11)
      - Y.M.C.A. (Box 77, Folder 12)
      - Miscellaneous Correspondence - Women's War Work in Virginia (Box 77, Folder 13)
      - War Work and Relief Organizations - Overview (Box 77, Folder 14)
      - Godmother's League of Richmond, Minute Book, 11 September 1917 - March 1918 (Box 78)
      - Women's Munitions Reserve (2 scrapbooks) (Box 79)
    - War Letters and Incidents
      - Partial List of Letters (Box 80, Folder 1)
      - Ainslie, George (Vol. III, p. 1) (Box 80, Folder 2)
      - Ancarrow, Newton (Vol. III, p. 2) (Box 80, Folder 3)
      - Anderson, Karl B. (Vol. III, p. 2) (Box 80, Folder 4)
      - Anderson, Henry W. (Vol. III, p. 2) (Box 80, Folder 5)
      - Antonelle, Leone C. (Vol. III, p. 3) (Box 80, Folder 6)
      - Ashbrook, Clarence F. (Vol. III, p. 4) (Box 80, Folder 7)
      - Baker, Frank A. (Vol. III, p. 4) (Box 80, Folder 8)
      - Balick, John W. (Vol. III, p. 6) (Box 80, Folder 9)
      - Baylor, Bernard H. (Vol. III, p. 5) (Box 80, Folder 10)
      - Beecroft, Mary C. (Vol. III, p. 6) (Box 80, Folder 11)
      - Big Thunder, Robert (Vol. III, p. 6) (Box 80, Folder 12)
      - Blackford, Staige D. (Vol. III, p. 6) (Box 80, Folder 13)
      - Photographs of Charles Leighton Bradbury and Frank Miller Bradbury (Box 80, Folder 14)
      - Bradbury, Charles L. (Vol. III, p. 7) (Box 80, Folder 15)
      - Bradley, George Younger (Vol. III, p. 7) (Box 80, Folder 16)
      - Breeden, Leo (omitted from Volume III) (Box 80, Folder 17)
      - Brown, Elisha W. (Vol. III, p. 9) (Box 80, Folder 18)
      - Claisch, Harold E. (Vol. III, p. 10) (Box 80, Folder 19)
      - Campbell, C.A. (Vol. III, p. 10) (Box 80, Folder 20)
      - Campbell, Irving E. (Vol. III, p. 10) (Box 80, Folder 21)
      - "Carlisle" (omitted from Volume III) (Box 80, Folder 22)
      - Carlon, Mary (Vol. III, p. 10) (Box 80, Folder 23)
      - Carlton, Louis Gwin (Vol. III, p. 10) (Box 80, Folder 24)
      - Carnefix, Thomas M. (Vol. III, p. 11) (Box 80, Folder 25)
      - Chesnut, Alex B. (omitted from Volume III) (Box 80, Folder 26)
      - Clarke, G. Stanley (Vol. III, p. 12) (Box 80, Folder 27)
      - Cleary, James B. (Vol. III, p. 12) (Box 80, Folder 28)
      - Cocke, William H. (Vol. III, p. 14) (Box 80, Folder 29)
      - Cofer, Paul A. (omitted from Volume III) (Box 80, Folder 30)
      - Conrad, James Mitchell (Vol. III, p. 15) (Box 80, Folder 31)
      - Conrad, M.P. (Vol. III, p. 15) (Box 80, Folder 32)
      - Crane, Robert Earle (omitted from Volume III) (Box 80, Folder 33)
      - Davell, C.F. (omitted from Volume III) (Box 80, Folder 34)
      - Davis, Mrs. Westmoreland (Vol. III, p. 17) (Box 80, Folder 35)